Yunus Emre Kepenek

Full Stack Software Engineer based in Türkiye, İzmir with 3 years of professional experience with a focus on building engaging & accessible applications with TypeScript, React, Next.js, NestJS, and more.

yunus.emre.kepenek@outlook.com +90 552 461 32 03 github.com/yunusemre-dev linkedin.com/in/yekepenek yunusemre.dev

Relevant Experience

Full Stack Engineer · Radity

Sep 2023 — Present

Zürich, Switzerland

- Build, style, and ship more than 5 high-quality insurance portals for a
 diverse array of clients including THREE Insurance by Berkshire
 Hathaway, using technologies such as React, Next.js, Nest.js, Redux,
 JavaScript, TypeScript, Material UI, Figma, and more.
- Led a team that redeveloped clients' large-scale websites with modern technologies, resulting in a 30% increase in performance, SEO, and accessibility scores.
- Work alongside product & project managers, designers, and other engineers to transform creative concepts into refined digital experiences at an agile cadence.
- Emphasize Swiss-quality standards in every stage of development, ensuring reliability, efficiency, and precision in the digital solutions.

Full Stack Engineer · DT Cloud

Jan 2023 — Sep 2023

Antalya, Türkiye

- Developed high-end cloud services, laaS and PaaS software solutions using technologies such as React, JavaScript, TypeScript, Node.js, Chakra UI, Redux, Figma, and more.
- Implemented client-requested features, resulting in a 30% boost in user satisfaction and retention.
- Contributed to the development of end-to-end tests with Cypress, leading to a 20% decrease in the occurrence of errors and system failures.

Undergraduate Research Assistant · Ankara Science University

Mar 2022 — Jun 2022

Ankara, Türkiye

- Guided and tutored 8 computer engineering students at Ankara Science University in OOP and Java, resulting in all students passing with an average grade of BA.
- Through detailed explanations and relatable examples, helped students grasp the fundamental concepts of Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) and the Java programming language.

Education

Software Engineering · Ankara Science University

GPA: 3.5/4 Ankara, Türkiye

Relevant coursework:

- Web Design and Programming
- Advanced Web Design with React

Skills

Programming Languages

JavaScript (ES2015+), TypeScript, HTML, CSS, Java, Python, SQL

Libraries & Frameworks

React, Node.js, Next.js, Nest.js, Svelte, SvelteKit, Astro, Tailwind CSS, Framer Motion, Redux, Zustand, Playwright, Express

Tools & Platforms

PostgreSQL, Git, GitHub, GitLab, Azure, Redis, Vercel, Heroku, WordPress, Docker, Webpack, Figma

Commercial Projects

threeinsurance.com · Radity radity.com · Radity tanitim.ankarabilim.edu.tr · Ankara Science University

Personal Projects

Studio · Storyboard Layout

Board · Custom Kanban Board

Self Shelf · Library App

Conversions · PDF Editor

Certificates

Meta Front-End Developer Professional Certificate

Received training from Meta, creator of React, upon completing 9 courses successfully.

Languages

English · Fluent **Turkish** · Native